Mercer West

 • Memphis, Tennessee, United States
 ■ mercerwest2@gmail.com
 □ +17063087398
 □ in/mercer-west
 ■ http://mercerwest.com

SUMMARY

Generalist looking to work with creative companies. 10+ years management experience with recent work managing people, projects, products and events. I am high energy and versatile. As a people person I gravitate towards management roles that serve customers and coworkers.

EXPERIENCE

Event Operations

Formula 1 Las Vegas Grand Prix

July 2023 - January 2024, Las Vegas, NV

- · Operations and Project Management for Year 1 of LVGP.
- · High profile client relations (Mercedes, AMEX, Richard Mille).
- Vendor management and project optimization in Smartsheet.
- · General management of complex, highly demanding timelines.

Product Manager

TURF TANK

August 2020 - May 2023, Svenstrup, Denmark

- · Voice of 5,000+ customers for international development team.
- · Roadmaps, UX / CX, Client Engagement, After Sales Relationships.
- Direct Manager for 8+ Technical Support and Client Success workers.
- · SME for hardware + software, Hubspot CRM, Atlassian, Dialpad.
- GTM strategy + launch of next-gen SW/HW platform in August 2022.

General Manager

YOUNG ATHENIANS

February 2017 - August 2018, Athens, GA

- $\cdot \ \ \text{Boutique graphic design firm specializing in packaging design, e-commerce and web design.}$
- · 100% ownership of business and client success management, reporting to founder and CEO.
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Clients included Creature Comforts Brewing Company, Palo Nutrition, and City of Athens.

Director of Projects

THE GOAT FARM ARTS CENTER

November 2013 - February 2017, Atlanta, GA

- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Real estate development firm with offices in Atlanta and New York City.
- Hybrid performing arts + studio center with 500+ residents + artists.
- Teams Manager for 300+ events on campus and around Atlanta, GA.
- · Collaborations with City of Atlanta and Newport Real Estate.

EDUCATION

Executive MBA in Strategic Leadership

Valar Institute at Quantic School of Business and Technology ⋅ Washington D.C. ⋅ 2024

Bachelors in Philosophy

Minor in Spanish, West African Literature \cdot University of Georgia \cdot Athens, GA \cdot 2004 \cdot 3.17

CERTIFICATIONS

Aha! Product Management Professional Certificate

Atlassian: Agile Project Management, Jira Software, Jira Service Management

HubSpot: RevOps, Inbound, Contextual Marketing, Marketing Hub, Sales Hub, Service Hub, Reporting

Microsoft: Project Management, Software Development, Data Analysis, Business Analysis, Generative AI

SKILLS

People management, Project management, Product management, Program management, Customer Success, B2B Sales, Team coaching, Remote work, Marketing, Data analysis, Data visualization, Social media, Ticketing systems, Jira, Confluence, CRM, HubSpot, Mailchimp, Google Workplace, Microsoft 365, Smartsheet, Adobe Suite, Contact centers, VoIP, Dialpad, SaaS portfolios, JavaScript, CSS, ChatGPT.